Every time the rain no longer falls, and I
see the sky, I think the rain is falling.
Back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry.
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger.
Bridery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead.
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now.
Though time's on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest of all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's not on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything.
Will take what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
living dangerously is one
thing living carelessly
another if i'd lack the foresight to bring
an antidote i'd be
stumbling over your corpses
right now don't ever
underestimate magellan
but we're here you shouldn't dismiss your
own inclusion your
presence is a factor in our
fate as well though
he's right i was sure i
was a dead man we're lucky
we're all still alive
well it ain't up to us whether we'll ever
die fear of death is
the fastest way to lose
just live what you can
even if it kills you right
still don't think i ain't
grateful for your help because
i am and again welcome to our
game i bet we'll make a great
team i don't see much future
for myself in this Carrot you're
exactly the sort of person i've
wanted to meet for some time
I'm afraid we'll have to do
without Inazuma from here.
Wait, are you trying to tell us
the infection is that serious?
I was lucky that Magellan hit
me with only one type of poison.
I was able to flush it out of my system
using my healing and energy hormones.
It's an ambivalent fix
though one hormone will
take years off my life while
the other causes severe
side effects so for him
the best thing possible is
good old-fashioned bed rest
and natural rehabilitation
nothing can help you to
regain the years lost
by using the hormone
Inazuma is an indispensable
newcomer of the revolutionary
army we need him healthy
so we have to make sure
he recovers slow and easy
Now that I think about it He wasn't
such a pain in the butt after all
He was Such a good guy
And he got God saving us
Hey, come on, guys.
It's sad, Nobby.
You can't waste your whole lives mourning.
He was great, but now he's
dead, and that's the way it is.
So all he can do is party.
That's what he would want.
So there you go.
It can double as a funeral for Mr.
Two.
What's the big idea?
It's the truth if you know it.
Hey,
for all we know, there's still a chance
Bond didn't even get killed, you big nose.
Oh, hey, what did you just say to me?
You got a big stupid nose to go
along with your big stupid face.
How about I stretch your
stupid face until it's...
Oh, blow it out your giant nose.
If you ask me, they both look like idiots.
Fancy trick how you rallied those
sharks how'd you do it i was under
the impression only mermaids have
the ability to speak to fish but that
impression is clearly incorrect is
that odd a fish man being friends
with fish well it's not the usual i
know that you're a strange one huh
The misfit of the savage species Fine
i'll take that as a compliment of sorts
Yes it's true Fishmen do have a violent
nature Vaughn is not dead, damn it!
Whoa!
Captain Buggy threw another big red nose!
Luffy
I wouldn't be here if it weren't for you!
You gave me the chance to rescue Ace.
And I owe you a great debt.
Don't think about it like that.
We're even.
And besides, you're super strong.
I'm just happy to have you on the team.
I wish I could thank him
properly and apologize
for my involvement in that
unfortunate situation.
But no, this isn't the time.
We have enough to worry about for now.
I only hope my strength will be enough.
I may be one of the seven warlords, but
they'll strip me of my title after this.
Now let's make Navy Headquarters
regret the ever-laid hands on Ace!
We must do right by our fallen.
We'll make your friend proud
and rescue Ace at any cost.
Warlord?
Navy Headquarters?
What?!
Whoa, really?
You're seriously a warlord?
Jeez, no wonder you're so strong!
Yes, I suppose I should
have told you sooner.
Everybody else knew that.
Hey!
What's all this talk
about Navy Headquarters?
Don't tell me we escaped
from the bowels of hell
just to head straight back
into the jaws of the beast!
Nobody is that crazy!
Surely you guys heard about the war
brewing between Whitebeard and the Navy?
Uh, war?
Navy Headquarters?
Don't act like it's a big surprise.
Not our fault you're so dense. Say what?
Well, we passed through the gate
of justice, isn't that right?
Our destination is Eni's lobby or Navy HQ.
This tub current is restricted
to government passage only.
It's one giant whirlpool that connects
the government's three major facilities.
The reason we bust it out now is because
we have a role to play in this war.
So you best get used to it.
Yeah, the real fight's about to start.
Real fight?
Then what do you call it back there?
No way!
No one told us about this! Stop!
Turn this ship around, you bastard!
Please, stop!
There's no stopping, and
there's no turning around.
Not while the ship's on the current.
If you're scared, just get off.
We can't do that, moron!
That would kill us!
We both have gallifruit power!
Maybe HQ, the warlords?
And the white-beard pirates all
fighting each other at once?
Nobody can survive that!
I've heard enough.
Please take me back.
I'd rather be in prison than this war.
All of us from New Common
Land knew about this plan.
Then why the hell didn't you tell us?
Hey, what is that?
You guys hear it?
That's just how I know what's here.
Click.
Uh, hello?
He answered it!
Greetings from Navy HQ.
Hey, move the here.
Idiot, don't say that!
Listen, kid, we're aware that the
ship has been hijacked by escapees.
We received a report from Impel
Down, so let's be honest here.
Before contact was lost, we had
insider information being fed to us.
Based on this, we've determined who the
two ringleaders behind the breakout are.
Two?
You, the pirate known as Straw Hat
Luffy, and another notorious pirate,
Buggy the Clown.
Wait, what? Ringleader? Seriously?
We've got warlords here, and their
main suspect is Captain Buggy?
Who the hell are you?
Come clean with us!
No, why me?
Pass me the documents.
Here.
Thank you.
At first, we just assumed that the
clown was another two-bit criminal.
But to be frank, we were wrong.
We learned he was a crew member on the ship
of Gold Roger, King of the Pirates. Ah!
They found me out!
You brutal me, Liar Jackson! Unbelievable!
You're a star!
A star among pirates!
Oh, and there's one other thing.
He's an ally of one of the four emperors.
His name is Red-Haired Shanks.
Are you serious?
So,
if you can hear us, Buggy,
we don't know how someone with your
background has laid low for so long,
but you most certainly stepped
into the spotlight now.
Well?
We haven't defined your
connection with Firefist Ace yet,
but we're sure you share the
same goal with Straw Hat Luffy,
to rescue him from execution.
Not really.
We know that you're accompanied
by Jinbei, Crocodile, Ivankov,
Not to mention the more
than 200 average run-of
-the-mill ruffians you tricked
into following your lead.
Now let me explain your future.
Your fates depend on whether
we open the gate of justice.
As long as we leave it closed,
you can't get to Marine Corps.
And you can't even get
out of the tub current.
You will be completely stranded.
There is no sea for you to escape to.
Better get used to your surroundings.
That's all.
Hey, wait, Navy! Huh?
I'm gonna rescue Ace no matter what!
Better keep your potatoes peeled!
Or what?
What?!
The things keep your eyes peeled!
Now I'm gonna be craving potatoes!
Thanks a lot, pal!
He just tried to pick
a fight with Navy HQ.
Forget the potatoes!
Wait, I've gotta know, Captain Buggy.
Were you honestly a member
of Goldraunch's crew?
And a sworn brother of red-haired shanks?
You should have said, you're one
hell of a pirate, Captain Buggy!
Now, hold on!
God damn it!
The government's not going to let me out
of their sights now that the truth's out!
Not the background I
was expecting from him.
And yet he's so weak.
That pedigree?
And he's so petty?
Every ship has one.
A little blemish, I mean.
Shut your mouth you know
actually perhaps you've
heard of a pirate named
Buggy from the East Blue.
The old vice captain
guy said something about
you the vice captain yeah
the old guy Rayleigh.
You know him right do I
are you saying that you've
actually seen Rayleigh
oh man I miss that guy.
Why'd you see him?
They're talking about Dark King Rayleigh.
Like it's no big deal.
Holy crap, Captain Boogie.
I knew you were the genuine article.
No, look, not so fast.
Everything is true, yes, but you can't
go spreading this around willy-nilly.
We gotta think about
my future as a pirate.
Wow, I can't believe you're a
member of such a legendary crew.
Boogie, Boogie, Boogie.
Hey, listen to me, you fool.
Boogie, Boogie.
Shut up already!
I was an apprentice, that's all!
You can't worship me for that!
Come on, knock it off!
I'm not being humble, just stop!
I don't feel as bad as I thought I would.
Oh, wait a minute.
Sure, the Navy has
completely overestimated me,
but maybe that's not such a bad thing.
Maybe.
That's because it's all true.
I've got a pretty good
reputation going for me here.
If only there was some way.
If I could defeat Whitebeard, maybe I
could become one of the four emperors.
Hell yes!
I would need to become
the king of the pirates!
It's perfect.
Some of these guys have probably got
higher bounties on their heads than I do.
If I play my cards just right,
I can do this.
Captain Buggy, we'll follow
you until the day we die.
Just give us an order, like steal
this ship from the guys who stole it.
We don't have to go to Navy HQ.
That's right, and then we'll be free.
Sorry to do it, Straw Hat, but
we're taking control of this ship.
We already broke out of prison, and we
don't want dying to be the next thing we do.
Surrender now.
We've got Captain Buggy on our side.
Tell him, Captain Buggy.
Not good.
Only one way to handle this. Kill us.
Good. I've got this.
I really think I can do it.
That's enough!
Don't get too flashy!
You guys are high on power
and acting impulsively!
No matter what, this ship's not stopping!
We're headed straight
for the heart of the war.
And you guys are already
on board, aren't you?
Think about what that means for a second!
In no time at all We'll
come face to face with
a man standing With his
foot on top of the world
Chances like this don't come
around More than once in a lifetime
So listen I want all of you to
live out a dream With me for today
I'll conquer Whitebeard And
thus rule the world Yeah
Captain Bunny
Captain Buggy
Thank you The darkness of hell
had beaten us down You saved
us Gave us light We almost lost
the most important thing Yes,
our dreams You fled us dream
again I'll follow you anywhere,
Captain Buggy To hell with
living a peaceful life
All right then, now let's win
this war, you guys, to Navy HQ!
So I guess the mutiny's over?
Then he's not entirely useless, I suppose.
You're gonna rule the world, Captain!
I know it!
I'm with you to the bitter end!
That's right you are!
Let them have fun while they can.
On the island of Marineford,
home of Navy headquarters,
there lies a large city primarily
populated by Navy families, but not today.
For their safety, an evacuation order
has been issued to all residents.
At the evacuation site on the Sabo
Odi archipelago That has placed
residents anxiously wait to view
the execution on giant monitors
Journalists and cameramen from
across the world have also gathered
here To break the news of the
proceedings as quickly as they unfold
Jeez the navy's really
not messing around that's
the best they've got
Yeah Whitebeard's gotta
know what's in store
so the question is does
he want to Risk it every
lookout ship the navy
has sent out in search
of Whitebeard has Been
swiftly sunk and yet there
have been no sightings
of the pirate himself
The tension looming of
a Marineford rises with
each passing second.
Start climbing.
Luffy, listen.
There's only one way to live life,
and that's without any regrets.
Uh-huh!
Someday, we're going to head out to sea,
and live the way we want to
live, more free than anyone else.
You think Whitebeard's gotten there yet?
There are only three hours left now.
Meh, I'm starting to wonder if
he's going to show up at all.
I know the guy's serious news, but
isn't he a little bit too old for a war?
Hmm, you really think so?
He's been tearing up the sea
since before the Great Pirate era.
Do the math, he's got to be senile.
And it's been a few years now
since his name made any headlines.
You're all fools for
taking this so lightly.
Whitebeard's living in a
completely different era now.
Does he stand a chance,
taking on the entire Navy?
It's bound to be a colossal
massacre, no matter who wins.
Let's just hope he doesn't show.
The execution would happen, but
one death is better than thousands.
You want me to open the
bar on a day like this?
The whole world's about to
go to war any minute now!
Just go back home!
I'll open up tomorrow if
we're all still alive!
And some bottles to go.
There's no reason for you to treat
us like we're on the execution block.
You expect us to live without drinking?
Everyone talks like he's just some old
man, but we all know it ain't true.
How long has it been now?
Couldn't have been more
than a year since he
walked in here and sat
right there across from me.
We all thought we were dead men.
Is Whitebeard really as nefarious
as everyone makes him out to be?
You're kidding?
Even those kids know.
Just listen to their little song.
White beer, white beer,
he's so mean, he's so mean!
Oh, Lord, I'm so afraid.
Where is this world headed?
Please help us through these awful times.
Get those in place!
You, pick up the pace, now!
Don't let your guard down!
No matter what we face,
it'll only last three hours!
After that, it's all over!
The Navy has summoned its most elite
soldiers from all over the world,
totaling almost 100,000.
With a focus on the
crescent-shaped Bay Area,
the island is protected
by 50 Navy warships.
On top of that,
the surrounding walls have been armed
with a countless number of cannons
and positioned front and center before
the vast throng of marshaled forces.
Stand five of the Navy's
most ferocious allies,
the seven warlords of
the sea, closely guarding
the scaffold from the
foot of the structure,
both revered and feared, the three marine?
admirals.
On this day,
every force of order the world government
can gather has been unified to stand
against the white-beard pirates in
imminent battle over the life of one man.
I can see it! Hey!
Jibay!
It's the Gate of Justice! We made it!
It was really fast!
It should have been faster.
We would have arrived a lot sooner
if the winds had been right.
The question now is how we're
supposed to get through the gate.
Well, men, you know what time it is? Huh?
Let me hear it now.
It's time for Captain Page
to cover the entire world!
And let me hear the rest!
Maybe HQ's going down!
Hey, look!
They're bringing out Firefist Ace!
Wow so that's him he
looks just like anyone
else but every step he
takes could throw all of
us into an unthinkable
war alive or dead he's
responsible for our fates
and the whole worlds?
Okay, Gar, I'll do the talking.
Go ahead.
I'll be waiting downstairs.
Step aside for a minute yes, sir.
It's the fleet admiral.
What's he doing pass me a snail sir
I have some information
you all need to hear
This man is Portgas D. Ace,
and the significance of his impending demise
is more profound than you may realize.
None of this is your fault, Garp.
Can't hold back those motherly
feelings during dark time, Tsuru.
Ace, I would like you to tell
them the name of your father.
his father what's that
have to do with anything
the name of my father is whitebeard not
true yes it is whitebeard is my father
my only father we launched a painstaking
and exhaustive search for you around the
time of your birth when we heard rumors
that your father had a child we took them
very seriously thanks to Cipher pole a
small but reliable amount of information was
presented to us based on this we checked
all newborns as well as all pre-born
children we spoke to many mothers but no
matter how far and wide
we searched we couldn't
find you no surprise
though especially when
you consider the lengths your mother went
to to hide you she performed a miracle that
can only come from the love of a mother
As a result, she misled the navy
No, she managed to mislead the world
You come from an island in
the south blue called Badalina
And your mother's name?
Portgas de Rouge
She pulled off a feat that
completely defied the laws of nature.
All to protect her child!
She kept her baby inside her
womb for an entire 20 months.
No, that's impossible.
And once she finally gave birth to you,
she lost all of her strength and
passed away right then and there.
And thus, a year and three months
after the death of his father,
a child was born with the blood of the
world's most odious villain in his veins.
That child was you!
Surely you must know the truth!
They can't persecute someone
who's yet to be born.
Right, Garpu?
So please look after my child.
You're a true father!
Is Gold Roger the King of the Pirates?